<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Wedding Singer Hire UK</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/</link>
	<description>Beautiful and Unforgettable Performances</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 15:22:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/cropped-Hartley_voices_church_Singers-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Wedding Singer Hire UK</title>
	<link>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Thomas, baritone</title>
		<link>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/thomas-baritone</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[weddingsinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 13:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Singers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Baritone Singer hire]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Book baritone funeral singer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/?p=100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas, bass-baritone, graduated from the Guildhall School of Music and Drama, where he won the English Song Prize. Since graduation with distinction in 2009 he has performed the title role in many productions including Rossini’s Il Signor Bruschino for British Youth Opera and Marcello and Schaunard in OperaUpClose’s Olivier Award-winning La Boheme at the Soho &#8230; <a href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/thomas-baritone" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Thomas, baritone"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/thomas-baritone">Thomas, baritone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignright wp-image-160 size-medium" src="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Tom_bass-baritone-232x300.jpg" alt="" width="232" height="300" srcset="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Tom_bass-baritone-232x300.jpg 232w, https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Tom_bass-baritone-768x992.jpg 768w, https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Tom_bass-baritone-793x1024.jpg 793w, https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Tom_bass-baritone-1200x1550.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 232px) 85vw, 232px" />Thomas, bass-baritone, graduated from the Guildhall School of Music and Drama, where he won the English Song Prize. Since graduation with distinction in 2009 he has performed the title role in many productions including Rossini’s Il Signor Bruschino for British Youth Opera and Marcello and Schaunard in OperaUpClose’s Olivier Award-winning La Boheme at the Soho Theatre.</p>
<p>Previously a choral scholar at New College, Oxford, Thomas has continued a successful performing career as Dulcamara L’Elisir d’amore, Alidoro La Cenerentola, CIA director Manifest Destiny 2011 both for OperaUpClose, Marullo Rigoletto (Bury Court Opera), Lesbo Agrippina (Barber Opera), Frank Die Fledermaus (Bloomsbury Opera), Morales Carmen (Kentish Opera), Mr Slender/Bardolph in Salieri’sFalstaff and Erimante in Cavalli’s Erismena both for New Chamber Opera, and Benoit/Alcindoro La Boheme for British Youth Opera once again. Other past roles include Belcore, Onegin, Count Almaviva and Mozart’s Figaro; other operatic work includes chorus for ENO, Garsington and Grange Park Opera.</p>
<p>Highlights of his concert work include The Messiah with the Cyprus Symphony Orchestra in Nicosia, the song project Lads in their hundreds directed by Iain Burnside at Kings Place and on BBC Radio 3, in which his contribution was singled out by Opera Now magazine as ‘a tour de force’, and Ives’ General William Booth enters the Kingdom of Heaven with Sir Andrew Davis and the BBCSO at the Barbican Hall. Other oratorio repertoire recently performed includes Bach’s St John Passion, Cantata 140 Wachet Auf and B minor Mass, Rossini’s Petite Messe Solonelle, and Haydn’s Nelson Mass. He has also sung with the Mark Morris Dance Company on their 2009 UK tour performing Schubert lieder at venues including Sadler’s Wells, Cardiff’s Millenium Centre and Snape Maltings.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/thomas-baritone">Thomas, baritone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alberto, tenor</title>
		<link>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/alberto</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[weddingsinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 13:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Singers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funeral Tenor for hire]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/?p=95</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Alberto, an experienced tenor, was born in Madeira, Portugal, in 1983. Before moving to London, Alberto graduated with his degree in Vocal Performance and Teaching at Universidade de Aveiro with António Salgado. He won the first prize at the “3º Prémio José Augusto Alegria” for young singers in 2009. He has recently finished the Guildhall &#8230; <a href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/alberto" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Alberto, tenor"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/alberto">Alberto, tenor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignright wp-image-162 size-medium" src="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Alberto2-260x300.jpg" alt="" width="260" height="300" srcset="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Alberto2-260x300.jpg 260w, https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Alberto2.jpg 282w" sizes="(max-width: 260px) 85vw, 260px" />Alberto, an experienced tenor, was born in Madeira, Portugal, in 1983. Before moving to London, Alberto graduated with his degree in Vocal Performance and Teaching at Universidade de Aveiro with António Salgado. He won the first prize at the “3º Prémio José Augusto Alegria” for young singers in 2009. He has recently finished the Guildhall School of Music and Drama Opera Course.<br />
Alberto was a student of the 2011 edition of the Solti Te Kanawa Accademia di Bel Canto (STKA), where he studied with Dame Kiri Te Kanawa and Sir Thomas Allen and prepared the roles of Nemorino, Ramiro and Almaviva with Jonathan Papp (RAM) and Corradina Caporello (Juilliard).</p>
<p>His main operatic roles include Monostatos Die Zauberflöte Mozart, Orfée Orfée aux Enfers Offenbach, Macheath Die Dreigroschenoper Kurt Weill, Gherardo Gianni Schicchi Puccini, Boy 1 Trouble in Tahiti Bernstein, Witch Hansel and Gretel Humperdinck, Leandro La Spinalba Almeida, Kaspar Amahl and the Night Visitors Menotti, LAumonier Les Dialogues des Carmelites Poulenc, Beppe Rita Donizetti.</p>
<p><strong>“Chris and I are sitting here much regretting that we never saw you again to thank you after your “encore” on Sunday. I’m afraid I got caught up with announcing something about cheese but I’m sure you realise how well you were received by our friends and how much everyone there enjoyed your…”</strong><br />
Cynthia Saunders, Ruby Wedding Anniversary Lunch Party, Hampstead</p>
<p>Alberto&#8217;s main oratorio roles include Te Deum Charpentier, Te Deum Bruckner, Messa Regina Caeli Pietro Yon, Messe in G Schubert, Missa in Angustiis “Nelson Mass”, Missa Cellensis CecilienMass, The Creation Haydn, Kronungsmesse Mozart, Oratorio de Noël Saint Saëns, Petite Messe Solennelle, Stabat Mater Rossini, Magnificat Bach, St. Paul Mendelssohn, The Messiah Haendel, Mass in F Heinichen (UK premiere).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/alberto">Alberto, tenor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lisa, mezzo-soprano</title>
		<link>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/lisa</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[weddingsinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 13:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Singers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[book mezzo-soprano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funeral Singer hire]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/?p=86</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lisa, mezzo soprano opera soloist, studied voice in Australia, Italy and the United Kingdom and completed a Masters of Performance (Opera) from the Sydney Conservatorium of Music, and a Bachelor of Music Education and a Bachelor of Arts (Music), from the Queensland Conservatorium of Music in Australia. She has worked as a professional singer for &#8230; <a href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/lisa" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Lisa, mezzo-soprano"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/lisa">Lisa, mezzo-soprano</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignright wp-image-157 size-medium" src="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Lisa_mezzo_2-225x300.jpg" alt="" width="225" height="300" srcset="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Lisa_mezzo_2-225x300.jpg 225w, https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Lisa_mezzo_2-768x1024.jpg 768w, https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Lisa_mezzo_2.jpg 882w" sizes="(max-width: 225px) 85vw, 225px" />Lisa, mezzo soprano opera soloist, studied voice in Australia, Italy and the United Kingdom and completed a Masters of Performance (Opera) from the Sydney Conservatorium of Music, and a Bachelor of Music Education and a Bachelor of Arts (Music), from the Queensland Conservatorium of Music in Australia.</p>
<p>She has worked as a professional singer for many years in Australia and the United Kingdom and has a wide range of professional performing experience. She has sung as a soloist at the Tri-nations Rugby League at Loftus stadium in London, the National Apex Conference, the Design Awards, and for audiences including the Australian Prime Minister at Angel Place Recital Hall in Sydney.<br />
Recordings include soloist for Telstra promotional video, Bolivar soundtrack (lead Manuela), and demo recordings for new composers.</p>
<p><strong>“Dear Lisa, I have just been watching the video which seems to capture it all very well. Your performance was most musical and sensitive and very well received and I am grateful to all the soloists for putting on such a great show. I look forward to opportunities to work with you again in the future. All the very best”</strong><br />
Bob (Verdi Requiem Performance, Birmingham Symphony Hall)</p>
<p>Opera work includes productions for Opera Queensland and Opera Australia in Australia, and many innovative companies in the United Kingdom. Roles performed include Orlofsky, Cherubino, and Siebel. Lisa also performs regularly with a classical and jazz ensemble in London at venues including Hampton Court House, Melbury House and Rivington Gallery in London.</p>
<p><strong>“Acting and stage presence….riveting….beyond praise….envelopes the audience and transports it…..”</strong><br />
Perform magazine, Review</p>
<p>Where accompaniment is concerned, she is also well experienced at singing with harpist, pianist, organist, string quartet, choir, a cappella, high quality recorded backing accompaniment and more. She is happy to work with musicians whom you’ve arranged independently, or to organise accompaniment per your request. If you are unsure of what you’d like, Lisa is happy to talk you through the options based on your venue.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/lisa">Lisa, mezzo-soprano</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Catherine, soprano</title>
		<link>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/catherine-soprano</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[weddingsinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 11:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Singers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funeral Singer for Hire]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/?p=82</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Catherine is an incredibly versatile female singer who flits from opera to jazz with ease. She has recently completed her studies at Guildhall School of Music and Drama, and is a member of the New London Chamber Choir. She graduated with her BAMus Hons from the University of Nottingham in 2003. Her performances include Cinderella &#8230; <a href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/catherine-soprano" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Catherine, soprano"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/catherine-soprano">Catherine, soprano</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignright wp-image-164 size-medium" src="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/cath-1-e1493043009604-238x300.jpg" alt="" width="238" height="300" srcset="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/cath-1-e1493043009604-238x300.jpg 238w, https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/cath-1-e1493043009604.jpg 527w" sizes="(max-width: 238px) 85vw, 238px" />Catherine is an incredibly versatile female singer who flits from opera to jazz with ease. She has recently completed her studies at Guildhall School of Music and Drama, and is a member of the New London Chamber Choir. She graduated with her BAMus Hons from the University of Nottingham in 2003.</p>
<p>Her performances include Cinderella in Steven Sondheim’s Into the Woods, alto solos in Bach’s Magnificat in D major and Schubert’s Magnificat in C major with the East of England Singers and the New Classical Players at Beeston Parish Church in Nottingham, and in ensemble with the College Chamber Choir, Girl’s Choir, and John Leggott Mixed Choir whilst at John Leggott College in Scunthorpe.</p>
<p>Catherine is active as a solo performer, both as a classical singer and with musical theatre. She has performed on the Palladium stage; at The Royal Albert Hall; The Palace Theatre and Westminster Abbey. She entertains regularly at corporate events and social functions, as a soloist and as a member of two professional quartets.</p>
<p>“The whole day was fantastic and the drinks reception was brought alive by Catherine and Andy’s wonderful music! Catherine was very accommodating with the repertoire of songs that we wanted and sang them beautifully. It made such a difference to have someone who was not only organised and professional but also sympathetic to the importance of the event for Lucy and I. We would not hesitate to recommend Hartley Voices and Catherine Fish to anyone looking for wonderful performers for an event. Thanks again, Kind regards, Will”</p>
<p>Catherine’s voice is often commented on for its ability to seamlessly adjust between classical and popular styles. Therefore, she is the ideal performer to match your specific event. Her voice would suit any religious or civil ceremony, reception, corporate event/society or recital using her varied and adaptable repertoire.</p>
<p>“Cath, I just wanted to thank you so much again for your singing at our wedding. I am SO delighted that I found you and decided to ask you to sing – I can’t bear to think that it was all done at the last minute and that we might not have had you! The ambience you created was unforgettable, really. You struck exactly the right note. Some of the most gratifying comments were from of the “tougher” contingent of our guests – namely some of the older men from Scarborough – who are usually very “matter of fact” about things. They all said they had lumps in their throats and were barely keeping it together!! You added to my personal memories of the day so much. I loved your choice of Casta Diva to walk into – it really gave grand status to the occasion and made me feel elegant and beautiful! You turned the (civil) ceremony from something I felt was going to be an anti-climax into the highlight of my day – which if I think about it, is really how it ought to be. Many thanks again, Sophie”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/catherine-soprano">Catherine, soprano</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sara, soprano</title>
		<link>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/sara-soprano</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[weddingsinger]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 14:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Singers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[soprano for funeral]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/?p=40</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sara is a truly unique soprano with an exquisitely warm, natural and intuitive voice. She earned her Masters Degree in with Distinction in Vocal Performance from the San Francisco Conservatory of Music where she studied with mezzo-soprano and vocal department chair Wendy Hillhouse. She enjoys performing for all of life&#8217;s person events and bringing a &#8230; <a href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/sara-soprano" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Sara, soprano"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/sara-soprano">Sara, soprano</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignright wp-image-166 size-medium" src="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/Sara_soprano_wedding-singer-232x300.png" alt="soprano wedding soloist, Sara" width="232" height="300" srcset="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/Sara_soprano_wedding-singer-232x300.png 232w, https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/Sara_soprano_wedding-singer.png 284w" sizes="(max-width: 232px) 85vw, 232px" />Sara is a truly unique soprano with an exquisitely warm, natural and intuitive voice. She earned her Masters Degree in with Distinction in Vocal Performance from the San Francisco Conservatory of Music where she studied with mezzo-soprano and vocal department chair Wendy Hillhouse. She enjoys performing for all of life&#8217;s person events and bringing a personal touch to every performance.</p>
<p>Her operatic lead roles include Gretel in Hansel &amp; Gretel, Susanna in The Marriage of Figaro, Loretta in Gianni Schicchi and Julie in Carousel. Amongst her achievements in competition she was recipient of the San Francisco Conservatory of Music Scholarship, Burlingame Music Club Voice Competition First Prize, California Federation of Music Clubs Competition Prize, St. Olaf Orchestra Senior Soloist, and the Winston Cassler Music Scholarship. Recently Sara has performed for events in venues including the Royal Opera House, Painters Hall, Grosvenor House, Park Plaza Victoria, The Wisley, Claridges, The Savoy, The Oracle Centre, Kew Gardens, Park Lane Hilton, Asprey, Lincoln’s Inn, Crown Plaza London, Oakwood Hall, Olympia Grand Hall, Gretra Hall, Christ Church Spitalfields, Sopwell House, Great Fosters, The Dorchester and many others.</p>
<div id="mp3jWrap_0" class="mjp-s-wrapper s-graphic unsel-mjp " style="font-size:18px;"><span id="playpause_wrap_mp3j_0" class="wrap_inline_mp3j" style="font-weight:700;"><span class="gfxbutton_mp3j play-mjp" id="playpause_mp3j_0" style="font-size:18px;">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span>&nbsp;<span class="group_wrap"><span class="bars_mp3j"><span class="loadB_mp3j" id="load_mp3j_0"></span><span class="posbarB_mp3j" id="posbar_mp3j_0"></span></span><span class="T_mp3j" id="T_mp3j_0" style="font-size:18px;">Tra bo dau - full track<span> - Sara Hartley</span></span><span class="indi_mp3j" style="font-size:12.6px;" id="statusMI_0"></span></span></span></div><span class="s-nosolution" id="mp3j_nosolution_0" style="display:none;"></span><script>
MP3jPLAYLISTS.inline_0 = [
	{ name: "Tra bo dau - full track", formats: ["mp3"], mp3: "aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZnVuZXJhbHNpbmdlcmhpcmUudWsvd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMTcvMDIvU2FyYV9IYXJ0bGV5X1RyYV9ib19kYXVfZGVtb18ubXAz", counterpart:"", artist: "Sara Hartley", image: "", imgurl: "" }
];
</script>

<script>MP3jPLAYERS[0] = { list: MP3jPLAYLISTS.inline_0, tr:0, type:'single', lstate:'', loop:false, play_txt:'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;', pause_txt:'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;', pp_title:'', autoplay:false, download:false, vol:100, height:'' };</script>
<div id="mp3jWrap_1" class="mjp-s-wrapper s-graphic unsel-mjp " style="font-size:18px;"><span id="playpause_wrap_mp3j_1" class="wrap_inline_mp3j" style="font-weight:700;"><span class="gfxbutton_mp3j play-mjp" id="playpause_mp3j_1" style="font-size:18px;">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span>&nbsp;<span class="group_wrap"><span class="bars_mp3j"><span class="loadB_mp3j" id="load_mp3j_1"></span><span class="posbarB_mp3j" id="posbar_mp3j_1"></span></span><span class="T_mp3j" id="T_mp3j_1" style="font-size:18px;">Lascia ch’io pianga</span><span class="indi_mp3j" style="font-size:12.6px;" id="statusMI_1"></span></span></span></div><span class="s-nosolution" id="mp3j_nosolution_1" style="display:none;"></span><script>
MP3jPLAYLISTS.inline_1 = [
	{ name: "Lascia ch’io pianga", formats: ["mp3"], mp3: "aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZnVuZXJhbHNpbmdlcmhpcmUudWsvd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMTcvMDIvU2FyYV9IYXJ0bGV5X0xhc2NpYV9jaGlvX3BpYW5nYV9kZW1vXy5tcDM=", counterpart:"", artist: "", image: "", imgurl: "" }
];
</script>

<script>MP3jPLAYERS[1] = { list: MP3jPLAYLISTS.inline_1, tr:0, type:'single', lstate:'', loop:false, play_txt:'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;', pause_txt:'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;', pp_title:'', autoplay:false, download:false, vol:100, height:'' };</script>
<div id="mp3jWrap_2" class="mjp-s-wrapper s-graphic unsel-mjp " style="font-size:18px;"><span id="playpause_wrap_mp3j_2" class="wrap_inline_mp3j" style="font-weight:700;"><span class="gfxbutton_mp3j play-mjp" id="playpause_mp3j_2" style="font-size:18px;">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span>&nbsp;<span class="group_wrap"><span class="bars_mp3j"><span class="loadB_mp3j" id="load_mp3j_2"></span><span class="posbarB_mp3j" id="posbar_mp3j_2"></span></span><span class="T_mp3j" id="T_mp3j_2" style="font-size:18px;">Micaelas Aria - demo<span> - Sara Hartley</span></span><span class="indi_mp3j" style="font-size:12.6px;" id="statusMI_2"></span></span></span></div><span class="s-nosolution" id="mp3j_nosolution_2" style="display:none;"></span><script>
MP3jPLAYLISTS.inline_2 = [
	{ name: "Micaelas Aria - demo", formats: ["mp3"], mp3: "aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZnVuZXJhbHNpbmdlcmhpcmUudWsvd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMTcvMDIvU2FyYV9IYXJ0bGV5X01pY2FlbGFzX0FyaWFfZGVtb18ubXAz", counterpart:"", artist: "Sara Hartley", image: "", imgurl: "" }
];
</script>

<script>MP3jPLAYERS[2] = { list: MP3jPLAYLISTS.inline_2, tr:0, type:'single', lstate:'', loop:false, play_txt:'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;', pause_txt:'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;', pp_title:'', autoplay:false, download:false, vol:100, height:'' };</script>
<div id="mp3jWrap_3" class="mjp-s-wrapper s-graphic unsel-mjp " style="font-size:18px;"><span id="playpause_wrap_mp3j_3" class="wrap_inline_mp3j" style="font-weight:700;"><span class="gfxbutton_mp3j play-mjp" id="playpause_mp3j_3" style="font-size:18px;">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</span>&nbsp;<span class="group_wrap"><span class="bars_mp3j"><span class="loadB_mp3j" id="load_mp3j_3"></span><span class="posbarB_mp3j" id="posbar_mp3j_3"></span></span><span class="T_mp3j" id="T_mp3j_3" style="font-size:18px;">Ave Maria by Caccini</span><span class="indi_mp3j" style="font-size:12.6px;" id="statusMI_3"></span></span></span></div><span class="s-nosolution" id="mp3j_nosolution_3" style="display:none;"></span><script>
MP3jPLAYLISTS.inline_3 = [
	{ name: "Ave Maria by Caccini", formats: ["mp3"], mp3: "aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZnVuZXJhbHNpbmdlcmhpcmUudWsvd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMTcvMDIvU2FyYV9IYXJ0bGV5X0NhY2lubmlfQXZlX01hcmlhX2RlbW9fLm1wMw==", counterpart:"", artist: "", image: "", imgurl: "" }
];
</script>

<script>MP3jPLAYERS[3] = { list: MP3jPLAYLISTS.inline_3, tr:0, type:'single', lstate:'', loop:false, play_txt:'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;', pause_txt:'&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;', pp_title:'', autoplay:false, download:false, vol:100, height:'' };</script>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/sara-soprano">Sara, soprano</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		<enclosure url="https://www.funeralsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/Sara_Hartley_Tra_bo_dau_demo_.mp3" length="1532427" type="audio/mpeg" />
<enclosure url="https://www.funeralsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/Sara_Hartley_Lascia_chio_pianga_demo_.mp3" length="1156705" type="audio/mpeg" />
<enclosure url="https://www.funeralsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/Sara_Hartley_Micaelas_Aria_demo_.mp3" length="827745" type="audio/mpeg" />
<enclosure url="https://www.funeralsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/Sara_Hartley_Cacinni_Ave_Maria_demo_.mp3" length="1431700" type="audio/mpeg" />

			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
