<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Funeral Tenor for hire &#8211; Wedding Singer Hire UK</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/funeral-tenor-for-hire/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/</link>
	<description>Beautiful and Unforgettable Performances</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 19:38:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.7.16</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/cropped-Hartley_voices_church_Singers-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Funeral Tenor for hire &#8211; Wedding Singer Hire UK</title>
	<link>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Alberto, tenor</title>
		<link>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/alberto</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 13:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[weddingsinger]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Singers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funeral Tenor for hire]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/?p=95</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Alberto, an experienced tenor, was born in Madeira, Portugal, in 1983. Before moving to London, Alberto graduated with his degree in Vocal Performance and Teaching at Universidade de Aveiro with António Salgado. He won the first prize at the “3º Prémio José Augusto Alegria” for young singers in 2009. He has recently finished the Guildhall &#8230; <a href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/alberto" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Alberto, tenor"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/alberto">Alberto, tenor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="alignright wp-image-162 size-medium" src="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Alberto2-260x300.jpg" alt="" width="260" height="300" srcset="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Alberto2-260x300.jpg 260w, https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Alberto2.jpg 282w" sizes="(max-width: 260px) 85vw, 260px" />Alberto, an experienced tenor, was born in Madeira, Portugal, in 1983. Before moving to London, Alberto graduated with his degree in Vocal Performance and Teaching at Universidade de Aveiro with António Salgado. He won the first prize at the “3º Prémio José Augusto Alegria” for young singers in 2009. He has recently finished the Guildhall School of Music and Drama Opera Course.<br />
Alberto was a student of the 2011 edition of the Solti Te Kanawa Accademia di Bel Canto (STKA), where he studied with Dame Kiri Te Kanawa and Sir Thomas Allen and prepared the roles of Nemorino, Ramiro and Almaviva with Jonathan Papp (RAM) and Corradina Caporello (Juilliard).</p>
<p>His main operatic roles include Monostatos Die Zauberflöte Mozart, Orfée Orfée aux Enfers Offenbach, Macheath Die Dreigroschenoper Kurt Weill, Gherardo Gianni Schicchi Puccini, Boy 1 Trouble in Tahiti Bernstein, Witch Hansel and Gretel Humperdinck, Leandro La Spinalba Almeida, Kaspar Amahl and the Night Visitors Menotti, LAumonier Les Dialogues des Carmelites Poulenc, Beppe Rita Donizetti.</p>
<p><strong>“Chris and I are sitting here much regretting that we never saw you again to thank you after your “encore” on Sunday. I’m afraid I got caught up with announcing something about cheese but I’m sure you realise how well you were received by our friends and how much everyone there enjoyed your…”</strong><br />
Cynthia Saunders, Ruby Wedding Anniversary Lunch Party, Hampstead</p>
<p>Alberto&#8217;s main oratorio roles include Te Deum Charpentier, Te Deum Bruckner, Messa Regina Caeli Pietro Yon, Messe in G Schubert, Missa in Angustiis “Nelson Mass”, Missa Cellensis CecilienMass, The Creation Haydn, Kronungsmesse Mozart, Oratorio de Noël Saint Saëns, Petite Messe Solennelle, Stabat Mater Rossini, Magnificat Bach, St. Paul Mendelssohn, The Messiah Haendel, Mass in F Heinichen (UK premiere).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/alberto">Alberto, tenor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
