<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Baritone Singer hire &#8211; Wedding Singer Hire UK</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/tag/baritone-singer-hire/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/</link>
	<description>Beautiful and Unforgettable Performances</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 21:30:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.7.16</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/cropped-Hartley_voices_church_Singers-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Baritone Singer hire &#8211; Wedding Singer Hire UK</title>
	<link>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Thomas, baritone</title>
		<link>https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/thomas-baritone</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 13:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[weddingsinger]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Singers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Baritone Singer hire]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Book baritone funeral singer]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/?p=100</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas, bass-baritone, graduated from the Guildhall School of Music and Drama, where he won the English Song Prize. Since graduation with distinction in 2009 he has performed the title role in many productions including Rossini’s Il Signor Bruschino for British Youth Opera and Marcello and Schaunard in OperaUpClose’s Olivier Award-winning La Boheme at the Soho &#8230; <a href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/thomas-baritone" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Thomas, baritone"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/thomas-baritone">Thomas, baritone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="alignright wp-image-160 size-medium" src="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Tom_bass-baritone-232x300.jpg" alt="" width="232" height="300" srcset="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Tom_bass-baritone-232x300.jpg 232w, https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Tom_bass-baritone-768x992.jpg 768w, https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Tom_bass-baritone-793x1024.jpg 793w, https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/wp-content/uploads/2017/03/Tom_bass-baritone-1200x1550.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 232px) 85vw, 232px" />Thomas, bass-baritone, graduated from the Guildhall School of Music and Drama, where he won the English Song Prize. Since graduation with distinction in 2009 he has performed the title role in many productions including Rossini’s Il Signor Bruschino for British Youth Opera and Marcello and Schaunard in OperaUpClose’s Olivier Award-winning La Boheme at the Soho Theatre.</p>
<p>Previously a choral scholar at New College, Oxford, Thomas has continued a successful performing career as Dulcamara L’Elisir d’amore, Alidoro La Cenerentola, CIA director Manifest Destiny 2011 both for OperaUpClose, Marullo Rigoletto (Bury Court Opera), Lesbo Agrippina (Barber Opera), Frank Die Fledermaus (Bloomsbury Opera), Morales Carmen (Kentish Opera), Mr Slender/Bardolph in Salieri’sFalstaff and Erimante in Cavalli’s Erismena both for New Chamber Opera, and Benoit/Alcindoro La Boheme for British Youth Opera once again. Other past roles include Belcore, Onegin, Count Almaviva and Mozart’s Figaro; other operatic work includes chorus for ENO, Garsington and Grange Park Opera.</p>
<p>Highlights of his concert work include The Messiah with the Cyprus Symphony Orchestra in Nicosia, the song project Lads in their hundreds directed by Iain Burnside at Kings Place and on BBC Radio 3, in which his contribution was singled out by Opera Now magazine as ‘a tour de force’, and Ives’ General William Booth enters the Kingdom of Heaven with Sir Andrew Davis and the BBCSO at the Barbican Hall. Other oratorio repertoire recently performed includes Bach’s St John Passion, Cantata 140 Wachet Auf and B minor Mass, Rossini’s Petite Messe Solonelle, and Haydn’s Nelson Mass. He has also sung with the Mark Morris Dance Company on their 2009 UK tour performing Schubert lieder at venues including Sadler’s Wells, Cardiff’s Millenium Centre and Snape Maltings.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/singers/thomas-baritone">Thomas, baritone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.weddingsingerhire.uk/">Wedding Singer Hire UK</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
